var rockQuestions = [
        
{//question 1:
question: "The wearing away of soil and rock by the action of streams, glaciers, waves, wind, underground water, and gravity?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Lithification", "b) Transportation", "c) Erosion", "d) Deposition"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Erosion"
},
    
{//question 2:
question: "The laying-down of rock-forming material by any natural agent?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Melting", "b) Deposition", "c) Metamorphism", "d) Intrusion"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Deposition"
},
    
{//question 3:
question: "Conversion of newly deposited sediment into a solid rock?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Extrusion", "b) Lithification", "c) Exhumation ", "d) Erosion"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Lithification"
},
    
{//question 4:
question: "Process of exposing previously buried rock at the Earth's surface by removal (erosion) of the material on top of it?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Extrusion", "b) Exhumation", "c) Melting", "d) Sedimentary Rock"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Exhumation"
},
        
{//question 5:
question: "Naturally occuring molten rock material generated and found within the Earth?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Magma", "b) Igneous Rock", "c) Lava", "d) Sedimentary Rock"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Magma"
},
        
{//question 6:
question: "Rock formed by cooling and solidification of lava above the Earth's surface",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Metamorphic Rock", "b) Intrusive Igneous Rock", "c) Extrusive Igneous Rock", "d) Lava"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Extrusive Igneous Rock"
},
    
{//question 7:
question: "A layered rock resulting from the consolidation of sediment",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Metamorphic Rock", "b) Intrusive Igneous Rock", "c) Extrusive Igneous Rock", "d)Sedimentary Rock"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],    
answer: "d) Sedimentary Rock"
},
        
{//question 8:
question: "Destructive process by which rocks are changed on exposure to atmospheric agents at or near the Earth's surface with little or no transport of loosened or altered material?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Deposition", "b) Erosion", "c) Exhumation", "d) Weathering"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "a) Weathering"
},
        
{//question 9:
question: "Solid Fragmented material transported and deposited that forms in layers of loose, unconsolidated material",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Lithification", "b) Metamorphic Rock", "c) Magma", "d) Sediment"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "d) Sediment"
},
        
{//question 10:
question: "Emission of magma onto the Earth's Surface",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Intrusion", "b) Erosion", "c) Exhumation", "d) Extrusion"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "d) Extrusion"
},
            
{//question 11:
question: "Movement of water through the soil surface into the ground?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Baseflow", "b) Through Flow", "c) Run off", "d) Infiltration"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "d) Infiltration"
},
            
{//question 12:
question: "Surface flow of water that appears after precipitation",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Run off", "b) Base Flow", "c) infiltration", "d) Through flow"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Run off"
},
    
{//question 13:
question: "Discharge of water to the atmosphere by plants?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Precipitation", "b) Condensation", "c) Transpiration", "d) Evaporation"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Transpiration"
},
                
{//question 14:
question: "Flow of water in the saturated zone under the influence of gravity?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Perspiration", "b) Precipitation", "c) Base Flow", "d) Transpiration"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Base Flow"
    },
                
{//question 15:
question: "Process by which water vapor becomes a liquid?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Transpiration", "b) Precipitation", "c) Condensation", "d) Infiltration"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Condensation"
}
];